<color=white>As you approach a gigantic magma dragon, a thundering voice comes down on you: <color=yellow>"Can't you see? I am enjoying my watermelon. This is just the right size for me. Stop bothering me." <color=white>You stand in shock, the dragon continues: <color=yellow>"Ah, you puny mortal, you have no idea you are speaking to the dragon god Arkath himself, right?"<color=white>. You nod furiously. The dragon god laughs: <color=yellow>"Come on now, tiny mortal. Don't be afraid. You quarrel with Elrath don't concern me. If you are interested in this delicious watermelon, I would like to give it to you, provided you can solve my puzzle. Rest assured you will never figure it out haha."<color=white><br><br>You insist to solve the puzzle, the dragon god then tells you: <color=yellow>"Find a me a hero at level 5 or below. You will have an army no more than a few Skeletons, I have 100 Magma Dragons, you have to defeat all of them in oneshot. If you can do that, I will let you taste this delicious half-watermelon."