<color=white>"Hi, traveler! <br>There is this hero, named "Valeria" past this monolith living in a quiet town. In her quest for revenge for the death of her father, she is willing to ally herself with anyone. Unfortunately she has gone too far and sided with Sheogh. Now she needs to be put down.<br>However there is a catch. Her town people love her dearly. They are fanatic about her. You will have to assassinate her outside her town, or else the villagers will burn their own town. Even if you just enter the town is enough to set them off. I don't want to see this happen.<br><color=green>If you can keep the town from harm and kill Valeria, I will teach you the spell Phantom Forces."