<color=white>"Hi, Traveler. I recently discovered an unknown creature on a secret island. It seems to be out of this world. Leaving him alone is not an option as he may summon more allies in meantime. I don't want the news of aliens breaking out in Ashan. It will cause unnecessary chaos.<br><color=green>Therefore I need someone to assassinate this creature and keep this information secret. if you can find a way back yourself, I will give you two Rings of Celerity as reward."