<color=white>"Hi, Child. I am the spirit who guides all who seek Sar-Elam's wisdom. Sar-Elam has known your struggle, and is willing to help you. Currently you cannot reach your beloved teacher, but that may be a good thing. If you face Freyda and her Elrath blessed army now, it would be a suicide misson. You will need a garrison town, with the Tear of Asha to deny her powerful spells. In addition, I can teach you two powerful forbidden spells if you can show you deserve it."