<color=white>"Of course the Dragon gods would not give up Tear of Asha to mortals easily. They created the most infuriatingly unfair and invunerable guardians to guar this artifact. When you are ready, visit the portal behind me to face a guardian of your choosing. <color=yellow>You may want to check with me on what each guardian will do before you go. <color=green>Once a hero has defeated a guardian, stand in the guardian cycle to activate the altar. Once all 8 alters are activated, you will have access to the A tear of Asha, which when built in town will prohibit Freyda from using light spells. <color=red>This means you will need 8 heroes at the same time. Once the Tear of Asha is dug out, all your heroes will be brought back. <color=white>After you have done that, I will send you to face Freyda."