<color=white>"Hi, Traveler. I know are busy fighting the dragon of light. However, the acts of Sheogh cannot be ignore, or demons will flood this land. I recently discovered an Inferno output somewhere underground. The demons, interestingly, were collecting troop from all factions. I have no idea what they plan to do with it, but it cannot be good. <color=green>Eliminiate all the dwellings and the output itself, and I will reward you two Cursed Rings."