<color=white>The nervous man finally squeeze out a smile: <color=yellow>"Ah, thank you, you found both of them!". <br><color=white>You dump the princesses from your backpack like a sack of potatoes.<br>This man continues:<color=yellow>"Here is your reward".<color=white><br>You suspect is this person is no ordinary man. He turned the princesses into treants, and is in possession of two rule-defying relics. However you don't have time for this at the moment, as you have a hero to save...