As you approach, this nervous man run to you and starts aksing: <color=yellow>"Have you seen any lost princesses?"<br><br><color=white>You replied:<color=cyan>"What question is that? How could some lose a princess like a wallet, not to mention more than one of them?"<br><br><color=white>The nervous man tells you:<color=yellow>"I am serious. I lost two princesses by accident. Please if you find them, pick them up and drop them here. I will compensate with two great relics, Pendant of Conflux and Mask of Equity. "