As, you approach, this farmer waves at you: <color=yellow>"Hi, young man. I have a field where I planted some Poltergeits, but now I have trouble harvesting them".<br><br><color=white>You are scratching your head, and replied: <color=cyan>"Poltergeits are not pumkins, you cannot harvest them on a farm land."<br><br><color=white>The farmer replies angrily:<color=yellow>"I don't care, <color=red>pull me those 800 Poltergeists out of the ground, and I will reward you Necklace of the Bloody Claw"