The thinking direction is: 1. Enemy will destroy the bulk of her own troops 2. You will need a way to become invunerable at the start and each time the enemy moves. 3. Your hero spells are not involved, since the enemy drain all your mana and uses counter spell. Therefore the answer is Haven hero with guardian angel to survive the first on-slaught, and griffins for the invulerability.<br><br>Having a haven hero with guardian angel, and wear the ring of speed and celebrity, and dragon wing mantle, now the griffin should have 20 initiative. Use griffin dive each time the enemy is about to move, and kill the last standed succubus with griffins and hero.