You should have all the spells and a high level hero at this stage. The secret to this fight is to use last stand vampirism on blood maiden. With raise dead on the blood maiden a few times, they become unkillable in one-shot. Then attack the black dragons such that they fire-breath will friendly-fire their own units. When there are only two stacks left, use the same tactic to keep both's amounts low. When either stack has about 100 left, kill the other stack with friendly fire, and use summoned units to kill the 100 black dragons easily.