The thinking direction is: 1. You have mana. 2. You are counter-spelled. 3. You units can barely move. Therefore, you need your hero to be your damage dealer, a hero that cannot be counter-spelled: barbarians.<br><br>Get all bonus creatures for war dancer and goblins, and from all 7 other towns tier 1, 2 and 3 into Shrine of the Netherworld in the necropolis town, convert them into undead creatures, use hordes anger on the dark guardian's troops. Careful not to carry too much troop, the dark guardian might charge in and you will suffer heavy loss.