The thinking direction is: 1. The enemy moves extremely fast and deadly, with anti-cheese to last stand tactics. 2. You will have no spells to use due to zero mana points and being couter spelled. 3. Enemy hero gets 0.5ATB discount everytime she moves. 4. Any corpse left by the enemy will be raised again. Therefore, you will need to disable their troops, and clear any corpse on the ground. The solution is a Demon Lord hero, leading an army of combat mages to counter the enemy mages.<br><br>Find a demon lord, learn the consume corpse ability. For your army, mentoring a high knowledge academy hero to give artifacts to 7 stacks of combat mages with armor crushing, attack and initiative. In tatic mode, place all the combat mages next to each other. Their auras will therefore protect each other from any mages' attack. Now the enemy troops are paralyzed. Focus your fire until an enemy troop becomes 1 hp, then one-shot it and use consume corpse to destroy the corpse.