The thinking direction is: 1. You have zero mana. 2. You face one-shot damage level from enemy troops 3. Enemy has counter-spell. 4. Bonus fire and ice damage negates any type of last stand cheese you are used to. 5. Enemy dispel any debuffs and immune to berserk. Therefore, you need a way to control your enemy despite no mana and being counter spelled.<br><br>Therefore the answer is ranger hero. With Arcane Training from sorcery, Sar-Elam's ring and a single archmage, the spell Wasp Swarm will has zero cost. Imbue arrow bypass any counter-spell attempt. With fog-veil and the archer's dream set, you can barely control enmey troops with wasp swarm. However, air guardian has an empty shield slot, drop the ogre shield with a sacrifical hero to him, now you can fully deny the enmy troops from moving at all. Ogre shield is non-transferable, but you can run away from the single peasant to drop it on ground. After that, you can use titans or any other ranged units as your damage dealer.