You have to use the skeletons to limit the golems' movement in this fight. AI will attempt to attack your unit while remain outside your attack range as much as possible. With two single-skeleton stacks, one serves as bait, one serves as scare, you can make the golems move one square at a time. Also, if possible, use the skeleton to drive golems to move into the opposite direction as well. This fight requires quite a bit of practice to make perfect.