The thinking direction is: 1. The enemy is immune to both physical and magic damage 2. Your hero cannot use any spells. Therefore, you need some other ways to deal damage. The answer lies within a necropolis creature Banshee. With enemy morale crippled to -5, this creature deal massive neutral damage that cannot be negated with magic immunity nor physical defence.<br><br> Use a necromancer, with banshee howl ability. You don't have to get the unique racial ability. Two rings of broken will plus cloak of death shadow should be enough. Use all the training quota to get knights, all the dark energy points to get wights. Then convert all tier 6 to banshees. Get 6 stacks of chieftain, each about 57, use order of the chieftain on the banshee stack, the enemy will vanish even before they move.