The thinking direction is: 1. Enemy has full magic immunity. 2. Enemy has too high defence 3. Enemy deny last stand cheese. 4. Your hero is not restricted, there is no mana restriction or counter-spell. Therefore the obvious answer is warlock hero to bypass the magic immunity with the Dungeon race trait. This hero is your main damage dealer.<br><br>Use mentoring to get a real high knowledge Academy hero to make the best artifact for magnetic golems with hp, initiative and defence. Then use firewalls to heal your single stack golems, use firewall or divine vengence to destroy your enemy.