<color=white>Black dragons are daughters of Malassa herself, though how she could birth so many children is a mystery nobody dare to ask. Being full immune to magic, these are no ordinary birdies. If you defeat all of them, I don't think any spell in Ashan can match your combat prowess. The only worthy reward for you, is the artifact set as black as the black dragons themselves: <color=green>Death's Embrace. <color=white>That is quite a fitting name for someone who defeated this many black dragons, right?