<h3>How to get spells<br><br><color=red>!Spoiler ahead!<color=white><br><br><body>For spells, Enlightenment is key. <br>One example is Arcane intuition. With this skill, you can fight the unkillable peasant, use your spell-casting unit to cast spell like haste or lightning. Then your hero can learn this spell. Some spells are tricky, you need certain conditions to cast them. For e.g., cleansing, you can seduce the peasant with Succubus Seducer, apply a buff to the peasant, then wait for the charm to wear off, then you can cast cleansing. Another is Raise Dead, you can use Druid Elder to cast earth spike to kill a single friendly unit, then use Lich Master to raise it. Lastly, ice bolt and circle of winter. You will need the Elemental Waistband to summon a Water Elemental to learn its spell.<br><br>Other than this, the rest of the spells can only be earned via quests. Do note Academy's unique skill, though they don't count towards the all spells reward. Once you have learned a spell, use Scholar (Englightenment) skill to pass them all to a single hero to claim your reward.<br><br>As for Runes, the rescued hero "Rune Magic Prodigy" can learn runes automatically upon leveling up. He has the same specialization as Inga from Fortress. You can use Mentor(Englightenment) skill to level him up. If there are certain runes not learnt, find the NPC that lowers your experience and do it over again.<br><br>For war cries, it is simple. The rescued hero Gottai has all the war cries. Make him learn Battle Lore (Barbarian Enlightenment) and pass it to a more useful hero on your side.