<color=green>For this challenge, all your war machines will be confiscated and your current army will be placed in a temporary but safe location.<br><br><color=yellow>In this fight, you begin with 0 mana, 6 Vermins.<br><color=cyan>You will face 70 Assassins, in a single stack. The win condition is to surivive this fight.<br><color=white>You will receive Ring of Machine Affinity, Shield of Crystal Ice, Bearhide Wraps, Armor of Valor and Ring of Caution as reward.