<color=green>For this challenge, all your war machines will be confiscated and your current army will be placed in a temporary but safe location.<br><br><color=yellow>In this fight, you begin with 0 mana, 80 Skeleton Warriors and 6 Skeletons.<br><color=cyan>You will face 40 Sprites. The win condition is to save all the Skeleton Warriors.<br><color=white>You will receive spell Sorrow, Eldritch Arrow, Fire Traps and Teleport as reward.