<color=green>For this challenge, all your war machines will be confiscated and your current army will be placed in a temporary but safe location.<br><br><color=yellow>In this fight, you begin with 0 mana, 4 lich masters and 200 skeleton warriors.<br><color=cyan>You will face 60 cerberuses. The win condition is all skeleton warriors have to survive.<br><color=white>You will receive Ring of Lightning Protection, Cloak of Sylana, Ring of Banishment and Boots of Magical Defense as reward.