<color=green>For this challenge, you can bring all the war machines you can find, but your current army will be placed in a temporary but safe location.<br><br><color=yellow>In this fight, you begin with your usual mana, 40 un-upgraded skeletons.<br><color=cyan>You will face 80 Pit Lords. The win condition is to survive the fight.<br><color=white>You will receive Golden Horseshoe, Four Leaf Clover, Tarot Deck and Crown of Leadership as reward.