So you are all the fuzz is about. Welcome to the Sanctuary. As the head of this small corhort here, I will like to test your magic abilities instead.<br>Any general wants to save as many as fallen soldiers. However, an arcane caster without access to divine spells can have difficulty in achieving this. Fret not, Sar-Elam himself placed an ancient effect in the arcane. This hidden arcane effect can save people's lives just like divine spells. Can you find this Sar-Elam's secret?