Good day!<br>Martial artists can dash across the battlefield with the blink of an eye, and seeming unstoppable at take the head of the enemy general. However, a seasoned commander knows, despite their physical appearance, these showmen are weak in their mind. A good commander can use his tatics to sow doubts in these showmen's minds, make them second guessing themselves. Are you such a good commander?