<color=white>"Hi, Traveler. I have a pack of wolves behind me. I have not socialized them well yet. I don't want to fight them and make them aggressive, but I also don't want them to stay here and hurt other passer-by. Can you find a way to scare them away peacefully?<br><color=green>If you can scare away those wolves peacefully, I will give you the Axe of the Mountain Lords and Dwarven Smithy Hammer."