<color=white>The previous elf seems to have a brother standing here :<color=yellow>"I have watched your fight with my brother. I think I recognize his mistake. I will devise a better combat challenge. Again, if you bring me a hero no more than level 5, I will give you some Crossbowman to challenge my sharpshooters. If you win, I will leave this place."<br><color=white>You realize this elf is certainly as arrogant as the previous one. Maybe teach him a lesson as well?