<color=white>An elf sharpshooter approach you: <color=yellow>"Hey, have you seen a thief who stole my unicorn?". <color=white>You shake your head. The elf then continues:<color=yellow>"Do you know, orcs are incredibly stupid? Unlike us elves, who are the smartest creatures in all of Ashan. These stupid orcs accidently built two buidings outside their main town. These two are behind me. How stupid can they be to do this? I just stand here menacingly, and they don't dare to cross." <color=white>You realize this is not a very nice elf, you have to teach him a lesson. You challenge his claim of being smart. The elf retorts: "<color=yellow>Oh, you think you are better than me? Come to me with a hero at level 5 or lower. I will give you some Crossbowman to fight me. If you can protect all the crossbowman against the Sylvan's best sharpshooters, then I will take my leave."<color=white><br>You realize this is obviously a trap, as Crossbowmen are much slower than the Arcane Archers, but his arrogance is so overwhelming you might just take the chance...