The guardian of Sylana has infinite protective power. Not matter how many troops you have or how hard they hit, they will do no damage to her. She will also protect her troops from all possible spell attacks with anti-magic barrier. It is not just protection, though. Don't be fooled by the name "earth dragon", her troops move as fast as lightning with her incredible initiative boost. Lastly, even if her troops fall, she will revenge every single one of them.