The guardian of Elrath has some feisty temper, paired with massive destructive power. She will attack your troops with fists of iron multiple times even before the fight starts. If you somehow survive the first shock, she will become even more angry, attack with mass Armageddon. Don't worry about her troops, she will have spells to revive those fallen by her friendly fire. Meanwhile, she has not forgotten about armor to protect her troops. Lastly, she will not let your have any mana to express your displeasure with her tactics.