The thinking direction is: 1. You have zero mana. 2. You face one-shot damage level of fire, earth and water spell. 3. Enemy has massive buffs and debuffs such as magic immunity and vampirism, followed by mass vengence and vulnerability. Therefore, you need a way to be immune to fire, earth and water at the same time, and also find a way to become magic immune and regeneration.<br><br>The answer is therefore dwarven hero with 0 mana cost rune spells on dwarven troops. Magma dragon is fire immune. Next, you can wear Cuirass of the Dwarven Kings to be immune to implosion. You can save/load a start sequence when the magma dragon uses elemental immunity rune, it gets water immunity. You can also skip the Cuirass of the Dwarven Kings and get a water and earth immunity. Use dwarven unique ability with resurrection rune to survive the first few rounds. When the fire guardian uses vampirism, steal it with magic control rune. Then steal the magic immunity from fire guardian as well. Due to programming oversight, magic control bypass any checks on if the creature is immune to the blessing he stole. Now you are immune to everything, and regenerate fully, the rest is just chore.