Since sprites are higher in both speed and initiative compared to skeletons, they will attack your skeleton warriors before you can make a move for sure. Therefore, surround your skeleton warrior stack with a bunch of single-skeleton stacks. Also, put 2 stacks at the opposite end of the battle field in tactic mode. AI's sprites will attack the single stack and avoid releasing the surrounded skeleton warriors if possible. Once they are near, move away the single stack and release your skeleton warriors.