<h3>From the Map Maker<br><body>Hi, everybody. I came from the Chinese HoMM5 community. I am a long time fan of this game. Since I joined the community since 2007, we have found many tricks and various ways to play this game. We had so much fun. In a way, we grew up with this game. Unfortunately most of us aren't good with English. Before we get too old, I decided to design a map that incorporates many of the techniques that we have found. Hopefully this map can make foreign HoMM5 players know us better. It also serves as a legacy for us.<br><br><h3>Credits<br><body>All the people who have helped me in my journey, I have made their names as NPCs you see throughout the game. Some of them had gone long time ago. Hopefully one day they will be back and see what we have accomplished. <br>In addition, I would like to thank the modder "aseguine" from NexusMod for providing many of the awesome models you see on this map. Please check out his work. I also need to thank the Russian Modding community for their awesome H5 scripting functions documentation (for e.g., hero.ag.ru website). Without their knowledge this map is impossible to make. Furthermore, I would like to thank RoundSweetPie, WindBellKL for their scripting help, and Piao and Pia for their map editor tips.