<color=green>For this challenge, all your war machines will be confiscated and your current army will be placed in a temporary but safe location.<br><br><color=yellow>In this fight, you begin with 0 mana, 150 Skeleton Archers and 6 Skeletons.<br><color=cyan>You will face 120 Steel Golems. The win condition is to save all the Skeleton Archers.<br><color=white>You will receive Helm Of Chaos, Ring of Caution, Ring of Vitality x2, Necklace of Victory and Book of Power as reward.