<color=green>For this challenge, all your war machines will be confiscated, and your current army will be placed in a temporary but safe location.<br><br><color=yellow>In this fight, you begin with your usual mana, 50 Crossbowmen.<br><color=cyan>You will face 120 Centaurs. The win condition is to save at least 80% of the Crossbowmen.<br><color=white>You will receive Golden Horseshoe, Four Leaf Clover, Tarot Deck and Crown of Leadership as reward.