<color=green>For this challenge, all your war machines will be confiscated and your current army will be placed in a temporary but safe location.<br><br><color=yellow>In this fight, you begin with 0 mana, 30 Arcane Archer and 6 Pixies.<br><color=cyan>You will face 60 Cerberi. The win condition is to save all the Arcane Archer.<br><color=white>You will receive Elemental Waistband, Trident of the Titans, Evercold Icicle, Phoenix Feather Cape and Emerald Slippers as reward.