<color=yellow><h3>Map Description<br><body>This map is designed to be a puzzle map. It's unlike your typical HoMM map. On this map, you start with unlimted resources, unlimited movement and unlimited mana(via dark ritual scroll) for all heroes. All experience, spells and artifacts can only be obtained via completing quest. You can get all spells and artifacts that exists in HoMM5 on this map. You army is fixed and there is no weekly growth for you. The enemy AI heros will not play fair and cheat on battlefield.<br><br><color=green><h3>Map Design<br><body>The main point of this map is to test your understanding of HoMM5. How much game mechanics you know, ranging from combat AI manipulation to various aspects of skills/artifacts, will decide how many quest you can complete. It is also important to use many different heroes and difference racial traits as possible, including dwarves and barbarians. Collaboration is key. You cannot beat this map with only a single hero.<br>The map is designed to have 3 stages. The first stage, you can complete the Sar-Elam's disciples quests. At this stage other quests are locked out. It is recommended to use a non-barbarian hero for this stage. The 2nd stage is where you complete many of the non-combat quests in the central area, and a few combat quests to boost your level to cap. The last stage is to challenge the 8 dragon guardians.<br><br><color=cyan><h3>Map Legends<br><body>All quest NPCs will have a rotating aura around them, and a glowing blue light near them. If you are not sure if an object is interactable, right click to view more information. All interactives should have proper right-click information, or else it is just decoration.<color=yellow><h3>Map Warnings<br><body>This map is test-played on heroic difficulty, with combat speed set to highest. Due to the heavy reliance on scripting and AI behavior, you may face many problems if these are not your settings.