<color=white>"Hi, I am ranger around these area. I often run into these weird statues that we call "Sphinx". There are 8 of them, and each of them will offer an artifact. I am too busy to check all these statues. If you can do that for me, present me with all the rewards you found from the Sphinxes, I will teach you three poweful spell: <color=green>Word of Light, Curse of the Netherworld and Armageddon"