<color=white>"Hi, Stranger. We have been training wolves to be more friendly. Many of us want to keep them as pets. I have a few good breed, but they are too few in numbers. Would you like to help us increase the number by 50x? I will give you 10 wolves. If you can <color=green>get back to me with 500 wolves, I will give you the Armor of the Forgotten Hero. <color=white>It is said to be the best armor in the world."