The guardian of Arkath has devastating destructive power that one-shots anything she touches,  but she will also drain all your mana to prevent you from doing the same. The fight is really a slow burn. At first, she does nothing. One turn later, a devastating Armageddon. Another turn? Armageddon with mass deep freeze. The next turn? Mass deep freeze, Armageddon and mass implosion. She would also apply mass poweful buffs here and there. If she still does not win after 7 turns, expect some mass Vengence and Vulnerability.