<color=white>As you approach a strange scene of a devil who corners an angel, the devil suddenly turns back and shout at you:<color=yellow>"Are you here for my Ms. Beauty as well? There is no way I am giving up. She isn't answering me, but I think she is just too nervous"<color=white>. You immediately noticed that this is just a case of harrassment. You ask the devil to go away, as the angel doesn't seem to be comfortable. The devil answers:<color=yellow>"Huh? You assume to command me? You know we devils are well-known for our bargains. If you can fulfill my bargain, I will leave. Find me a hero at level 10 or below, I will only give you an army of no more than 40 skeletons, to fight my 80 Pit Lords friends without magic. Hahahah, I know from your face you think this is impossible!"