这里的思考方向是：1.你有魔法；2.你被法术抑制了；3.你的单位基本没法行动。. Therefore, you need your hero to be your damage dealer, a hero that cannot be counter-spelled: barbarians.<br><br>Get all bonus creatures for war dancer and goblins, and from all 7 other towns tier 1, 2 and 3 into Shrine of the Netherworld in the necropolis town, convert them into undead creatures, use hordes anger on the dark guardian's troops. Careful not to carry too much troop, the dark guardian might charge in and you will suffer heavy loss.