For spells, Enlightenment is key.<br>One example is Arcane intuition. With this skill, you can fight the unkillable peasant, use your spell-casting unit to cast spell like haste or lightning. Then your hero can learn this spell. Some spells are tricky, you need certain conditions to cast them. For e.g., cleansing, you can seduce the peasant with Succubus Seducer, apply a buff to the peasant, then wait for the charm to wear off, then you can cast cleansing. Another is Raise Dead, you can use Druid Elder to cast earth spike to kill a single friendly unit, then use Lich Master to raise it. Lastly, ice bolt and circle of winter. You will need the Elemental Waistband to summon a Water Elemental to learn its spell.<br>Other than this, the rest of the spells can only be earned via quests. Do note barbarian's talisman, they are useful. Once you have learned a spell, use Scholar (Englightenment) skill to pass them all to a single hero to claim your reward.