The thinking direction is: 1. The enemy one-shot 10 stacks in 1 round. 2. The enemy has troops that is immune to everything 3. Your hero cannot use any spells. Therefore, an Academy hero is the solution to all these. With melting artifact ability, a wizard can resurrect 5 troops with the cost of 1.25 atbs. With empathy this is easily doable. Next, with gremlins hp buffed with mini-artifact, 900 gremlin can disable the magnetic golems and deal damage <br><br>Make good artifacts for two stacks of greemlins, one stack with initiative, armor crushing and attack, the other substitute armor crushing with hp. Initiative crafting is capped at 50%, which means a gremlin at 18 initiative can disable two stacks of golems. The remaining 5 stacks are just throwable troops with a simple artifact.