As for Runes, the rescued hero "Rune Magic Prodigy" can learn runes automatically upon leveling up. He has the same specialization as Inga from Fortress. You can use Mentor(Englightenment) skill to level him up. If there are certain runes not learnt, find the NPC that lowers your experience and do it over again. For the two level 5 runes, one is at the Arkath NPC shrine, the other is on a magic wind. Use a sacrificial hero to drop the wand on Wulfstan, then in the fight use Arcane intuition with puppet master to force the enemy unit to use the rune, so your hero can learn it.