<color=green>For this challenge, all your war machines will be confiscated and your current army will be placed in a temporary but safe location.<br><br><color=yellow>In this fight, you begin with 0 mana, 1 un-upgraded Cyclop and 60 Goblin Witch-doctors.<br><color=cyan>You will face 60 Firehounds. The win condition is to save the Cyclop.<br><color=white>You will receive Breastplate of Eldritch Might, Tunic of the Carved Flesh, Necromancer's Helm, Sword of Might, Edge of Balance and Moonblade as reward.