Good to see you, young man!<br>New soldiers often despair that they couldn't take down an enemy in one-shot. However, a seasoned soldider knows even water drops can wear down stone. It is not about how much damage you can dish out in one hit, but how many times you can hit your enemy. As little damage as it may seem, you will wear down any enmies given the time. Do you have such persistence in your combat?